<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<root version="4.8" dataversion="20241002" release="8.1|CoreRPG:7">
	<character>
		<abilities>
			<charisma>
				<bonus type="number">3</bonus>
				<save type="number">7</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">1</saveprof>
				<score type="number">16</score>
			</charisma>
			<constitution>
				<bonus type="number">4</bonus>
				<save type="number">4</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">18</score>
			</constitution>
			<dexterity>
				<bonus type="number">2</bonus>
				<save type="number">2</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">14</score>
			</dexterity>
			<intelligence>
				<bonus type="number">1</bonus>
				<save type="number">1</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">12</score>
			</intelligence>
			<strength>
				<bonus type="number">5</bonus>
				<save type="number">5</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">0</saveprof>
				<score type="number">20</score>
			</strength>
			<wisdom>
				<bonus type="number">2</bonus>
				<save type="number">6</save>
				<savemodifier type="number">0</savemodifier>
				<saveprof type="number">1</saveprof>
				<score type="number">14</score>
			</wisdom>
		</abilities>
		<additionalStorage>
			<current type="number">0</current>
			<max type="number">0</max>
			<remaining type="number">0</remaining>
		</additionalStorage>
		<adventurelist>
			<id-00001>
				<name type="string"> Base Inspiration Points = 2</name>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<name type="string"> Bonus Inspiration Points = 0</name>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<name type="string">Coms connected to - Biggus -rowan - nianh- yo</name>
			</id-00003>
		</adventurelist>
		<age type="string">128</age>
		<alignment type="string">Chaotic Neutral</alignment>
		<appearance type="string">6' 2" Taught to follow Gruumsh, she has softly green skin, Her eyes a soft red yellow. her ears showing the old linage of elf mixed into her family blood line. Pierced with 5 bands on each side, showing the equal sides of good vs evil, her family watched balance itself as the years have pasted. A symbol of her family passed down for decades. The chao of her dark hair following always free. </appearance>
		<background type="string">Gate Warden</background>
		<backgroundlink type="windowreference">
			<class>reference_background</class>
			<recordname>reference.backgrounddata.gatewarden@DD 5E Unearthed Arcana Players</recordname>
		</backgroundlink>
		<bonds type="string">I idolize a hero of the old tales and measure my deeds against that person's. \nI protect those who cannot protect themselves.\nMy life's work is a series of tomes related to a specific field of lore.  I have an ancient text that holds terrible secrets that must not fall into the wrong hands.</bonds>
		<classes>
			<id-00001>
				<cantrips type="number">0</cantrips>
				<casterlevelinvmult type="number">2</casterlevelinvmult>
				<casterpactmagic type="number">0</casterpactmagic>
				<hddie type="dice">1d10</hddie>
				<hdused type="number">0</hdused>
				<level type="number">7</level>
				<name type="string">Paladin</name>
				<rolls>
					<lvl-001 type="number">10</lvl-001>
					<lvl-002 type="number">10</lvl-002>
					<lvl-003 type="number">10</lvl-003>
					<lvl-004 type="number">10</lvl-004>
					<lvl-005 type="number">10</lvl-005>
					<lvl-006 type="number">10</lvl-006>
					<lvl-007 type="number">10</lvl-007>
				</rolls>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>reference_class</class>
					<recordname>reference.classdata.paladin@DD PHB Deluxe</recordname>
				</shortcut>
				<specialization type="string">Oath of Devotion</specialization>
				<specializationlink type="windowreference">
					<class>reference_class_specialization</class>
					<recordname>reference.classdata.paladin.abilities.oathofdevotion@DD5E SRD Data</recordname>
				</specializationlink>
				<spellability type="string">charisma</spellability>
				<spellsknown type="number">0</spellsknown>
				<spellsprepared type="number">2</spellsprepared>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<cantrips type="number">3</cantrips>
				<casterlevelinvmult type="number">1</casterlevelinvmult>
				<casterpactmagic type="number">0</casterpactmagic>
				<hddie type="dice">1d8</hddie>
				<hdused type="number">0</hdused>
				<level type="number">3</level>
				<name type="string">Cleric</name>
				<rolls>
					<lvl-001 type="number">8</lvl-001>
					<lvl-002 type="number">8</lvl-002>
					<lvl-003 type="number">8</lvl-003>
				</rolls>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>reference_class</class>
					<recordname>reference.classdata.cleric@DD PHB Deluxe</recordname>
				</shortcut>
				<specialization type="string">Life Domain</specialization>
				<specializationlink type="windowreference">
					<class>reference_class_specialization</class>
					<recordname>reference.classdata.cleric.abilities.lifedomain@DD Basic Rules - Player</recordname>
				</specializationlink>
				<spellability type="string">wisdom</spellability>
				<spellsknown type="number">0</spellsknown>
				<spellsprepared type="number">1</spellsprepared>
			</id-00002>
		</classes>
		<cohorts>
			<id-00001>
				<abilities>
					<charisma>
						<bonus type="number">3</bonus>
						<score type="number">16</score>
					</charisma>
					<constitution>
						<bonus type="number">1</bonus>
						<score type="number">13</score>
					</constitution>
					<dexterity>
						<bonus type="number">5</bonus>
						<score type="number">20</score>
					</dexterity>
					<intelligence>
						<bonus type="number">2</bonus>
						<score type="number">14</score>
					</intelligence>
					<strength>
						<bonus type="number">-4</bonus>
						<score type="number">3</score>
					</strength>
					<wisdom>
						<bonus type="number">1</bonus>
						<score type="number">12</score>
					</wisdom>
				</abilities>
				<ac type="number">15</ac>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<desc type="string">Melee Weapon Attack: +7 to hit, reach 5 ft., one creature. Hit: 1 piercing damage.</desc>
						<name type="string">Bite</name>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<desc type="string">The dragon exhales a puff of euphoria gas at one creature within 5 feet of it. The target must succeed on a DC 11 Wisdom saving throw, or for 1 minute, the target can't take reactions and must roll a d6 at the start of each of its turns to determine its behavior during the turn: 1- 4. The target takes no action or bonus action and uses all of its movement to move in a random direction. 5- 6. The target doesn't move, and the only thing it can do on its turn is make a DC 11 Wisdom saving throw, ending the effect on itself on a success.</desc>
						<name type="string">Euphoria Breath (Recharge 5-6)</name>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<bonusactions />
				<classes />
				<cr type="string">2</cr>
				<damagethreshold type="number">0</damagethreshold>
				<deathsavefail type="number">0</deathsavefail>
				<deathsavesuccess type="number">0</deathsavesuccess>
				<hd type="string">(4d4 + 4)</hd>
				<hp type="number">14</hp>
				<hpadjust type="number">0</hpadjust>
				<hptemp type="number">0</hptemp>
				<hptotal type="number">14</hptotal>
				<innatespells>
					<id-00001>
						<desc type="string">Level: 1\nCasting Time: 1 action\nComponents: V, S, M (a pinch of powder or sand that is colored red, yellow, and blue)\nDuration: 1 round\nRange: Self (15-foot cone)\nA dazzling array of flashing, colored light springs from your hand. Roll 6d10; the total is how many hit points of creatures this spell can effect. Creatures in a 15-foot cone originating from you are affected in ascending order of their current hit points (ignoring unconscious creatures and creatures that can't see).\nStarting with the creature that has the lowest current hit points, each creature affected by this spell is blinded until the end of your next turn. Subtract each creature's hit points from the total before moving on to the creature with the next lowest hit points. A creature's hit points must be equal to or less than the remaining total for that creature to be affected.\nAt Higher Levels. When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, roll an additional 2d10 for each slot level above 1st.\n</desc>
						<name type="string">Color Spray (1/day)</name>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<desc type="string">Level: 0\nCasting Time: 1 action\nComponents: V, S, M (a bit of phosphorus or wychwood, or a glowworm)\nDuration: Concentration, up to 1 minute\nRange: 120 feet\nYou create up to four torch-sized lights within range, making them appear as torches, lanterns, or glowing orbs that hover in the air for the duration. You can also combine the four lights into one glowing vaguely humanoid form of Medium size. Whichever form you choose, each light sheds dim light in a 10-foot radius.\nAs a bonus action on your turn, you can move the lights up to 60 feet to a new spot within range. A light must be within 20 feet of another light created by this spell, and a light winks out if it exceeds the spell's range.\n</desc>
						<name type="string">Dancing Lights (1/day)</name>
					</id-00002>
					<id-00003>
						<desc type="string">Level: 4\nCasting Time: 10 minutes\nComponents: V, S, M (a stone, a twig, and a bit of green plant)\nDuration: 24 hours\nRange: 300 feet\nYou make natural terrain in a 150-foot cube in range look, sound, and smell like some other sort of natural terrain. Thus, open fields or a road can be made to resemble a swamp, hill, crevasse, or some other difficult or impassable terrain. A pond can be made to seem like a grassy meadow, a precipice like a gentle slope, or a rock-strewn gully like a wide and smooth road. Manufactured structures, equipment, and creatures within the area aren't changed in appearance.\nThe tactile characteristics of the terrain are unchanged, so creatures entering the area are likely to see through the illusion. If the difference isn't obvious by touch, a creature carefully examining the illusion can attempt an Intelligence (Investigation) check against your spell save DC to disbelieve it. A creature who discerns the illusion for what it is, sees it as a vague image superimposed on the terrain.\n</desc>
						<name type="string">Hallucinatory Terrain (1/day)</name>
					</id-00003>
					<id-00004>
						<desc type="string">Level: 0\nCasting Time: 1 action\nComponents: V, S\nDuration: 1 minute\nRange: 30 feet\nA spectral, floating hand appears at a point you choose within range. The hand lasts for the duration or until you dismiss it as an action. The hand vanishes if it is ever more than 30 feet away from you or if you cast this spell again.\nYou can use your action to control the hand. You can use the hand to manipulate an object, open an unlocked door or container, stow or retrieve an item from an open container, or pour the contents out of a vial. You can move the hand up to 30 feet each time you use it.\nThe hand can't attack, activate magic items, or carry more than 10 pounds.\n</desc>
						<name type="string">Mage Hand (1/day)</name>
					</id-00004>
					<id-00005>
						<desc type="string">Level: 3\nCasting Time: 1 action\nComponents: V, S, M (a bit of fleece)\nDuration: Concentration, up to 10 minutes\nRange: 120 feet\nYou create the image of an object, a creature, or some other visible phenomenon that is no larger than a 20-foot cube. The image appears at a spot that you can see within range and lasts for the duration. It seems completely real, including sounds, smells, and temperature appropriate to the thing depicted. You can't create sufficient heat or cold to cause damage, a sound loud enough to deal thunder damage or deafen a creature, or a smell that might sicken a creature (like a troglodyte's stench).\nAs long as you are within range of the illusion, you can use your action to cause the image to move to any other spot within range. As the image changes location, you can alter its appearance so that its movements appear natural for the image. For example, if you create an image of a creature and move it, you can alter the image so that it appears to be walking. Similarly, you can cause the illusion to make different sounds at different times, even making it carry on a conversation, for example.\nPhysical interaction with the image reveals it to be an illusion, because things can pass through it. A creature that uses its action to examine the image can determine that it is an illusion with a successful Intelligence (Investigation) check against your spell save DC. If a creature discerns the illusion for what it is, the creature can see through the image, and its other sensory qualities become faint to the creature.\nAt Higher Levels. When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 6th level or higher, the spell lasts until dispelled, without requiring your concentration.\n</desc>
						<name type="string">Major Image (1/day)</name>
					</id-00005>
					<id-00006>
						<desc type="string">Level: 0\nCasting Time: 1 action\nComponents: S, M (a bit of fleece)\nDuration: 1 minute\nRange: 30 feet\nYou create a sound or an image of an object within range that lasts for the duration. The illusion also ends if you dismiss it as an action or cast this spell again.\nIf you create a sound, its volume can range from a whisper to a scream. It can be your voice, someone else's voice, a lion's roar, a beating of drums, or any other sound you choose. The sound continues unabated throughout the duration, or you can make discrete sounds at different times before the spell ends.\nIf you create an image of an object-such as a chair, muddy footprints, or a small chest-it must be no larger than a 5-foot cube. The image can't create sound, light, smell, or any other sensory effect. Physical interaction with the image reveals it to be an illusion, because things can pass through it.\nIf a creature uses its action to examine the sound or image, the creature can determine that it is an illusion with a successful Intelligence (Investigation) check against your spell save DC. If a creature discerns the illusion for what it is, the illusion becomes faint to the creature.\n</desc>
						<name type="string">Minor Illusion (1/day)</name>
					</id-00006>
					<id-00007>
						<desc type="string">Level: 2\nCasting Time: 1 action\nComponents: V, S\nDuration: 1 minute\nRange: Self\nThree illusory duplicates of yourself appear in your space. Until the spell ends, the duplicates move with you and mimic your actions, shifting position so it's impossible to track which image is real. You can use your action to dismiss the illusory duplicates.\nEach time a creature targets you with an attack during the spell's duration, roll a d20 to determine whether the attack instead targets one of your duplicates.\nIf you have three duplicates, you must roll a6 or higher to change the attack's target to a duplicate. With two duplicates, you must roll an 8 or higher. With one duplicate, you must roll an 11 or higher.\nA duplicate's AC equals 10 + your Dexterity modifier. If an attack hits a duplicate, the duplicate is destroyed. A duplicate can be destroyed only by an attack that hits it.\nIt ignores all other damage and effects. The spell ends when all three duplicates are destroyed.\nA creature is unaffected by this spell if it can't see, if it relies on senses other than sight, such as blindsight, or if it can perceive illusions as false, as with truesight.\n</desc>
						<name type="string">Mirror Image (1/day)</name>
					</id-00007>
					<id-00008>
						<desc type="string">Level: 4\nCasting Time: 1 action\nComponents: V, S, M (a caterpillar cocoon)\nDuration: Concentration, up to 1 hour\nRange: 60 feet\nThis spell transforms a creature that you can see within range into a new form. An unwilling creature must make a Wisdom saving throw to avoid the effect. A shapechanger automatically succeeds on this saving throw. This spell can't affect a target that has 0 hit points.\nThe transformation lasts for the duration, or until the target drops to 0 hit points or dies. The new form can be any beast whose challenge rating is equal to or less than the target's (or the target's level, if it doesn't have a challenge rating). The target's game statistics, including mental ability scores, are replaced by the statistics of the chosen beast. It retains its alignment and personality.\nThe target assumes the hit points of its new form. When it reverts to its normal form, the creature returns to the number of hit points it had before it transformed. If it reverts as a result of dropping to 0 hit points, any excess damage carries over to its normal form. As long as the excess damage doesn't reduce the creature's normal form to 0 hit points, it isn't knocked unconscious.\nThe creature is limited in the actions it can perform by the nature of its new form, and it can't speak, cast spells, or take any other action that requires hands or speech. The target's gear melds into the new form. The creature can't activate, use, wield, or otherwise benefit from any of its equipment.\n</desc>
						<name type="string">Polymorph (1/day)</name>
					</id-00008>
					<id-00009>
						<desc type="string">Level: 2\nCasting Time: 1 action\nComponents: V, M (a snake's tongue and either a bit of honeycomb or a drop of sweet oil)\nDuration: Concentration, up to 8 hours\nRange: 30 feet\nYou suggest a course of activity (limited to a sentence or two) and magically influence a creature you can see within range that can hear and understand you.\nCreatures that can't be charmed are immune to this effect. The suggestion must be worded in such a manner as to make the course of action sound reasonable.\nAsking the creature to stab itself, throw itself onto a spear, immolate itself, or do some other obviously harmful act ends the spell.\nThe target must make a Wisdom saving throw. On a failed save, it pursues the course of action you described to the best of its ability. The suggested course of action can continue for the entire duration. If the suggested activity can be completed in a shorter time, the spell ends when the subject finishes what it was asked to do. You can also specify conditions that will trigger a special activity during the duration. For example, you might suggest that a knight give her warhorse to the first beggar she meets. If the condition isn't met before the spell expires, the activity isn't performed.\nIf you or any of your companions damage the target, the spell ends.\n</desc>
						<name type="string">Suggestion (1/day)</name>
					</id-00009>
				</innatespells>
				<isidentified type="number">0</isidentified>
				<lairactions />
				<languages type="string">Draconic, Sylvan</languages>
				<legendaryactions />
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Tilrum the stubborn little dragon</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Tilrum the stubborn little dragon</nonid_name>
				<picture type="token">portraits/Companions/Tilrum the stubborn.png</picture>
				<reactions />
				<senses type="string">darkvision 60 ft., passive Perception 13</senses>
				<size type="string">Tiny</size>
				<skills type="string">Arcana +4, Perception +3, Stealth +7</skills>
				<speed type="string">10 ft., fly 60 ft.</speed>
				<spells />
				<spellslots>
					<level1 type="number">0</level1>
					<level2 type="number">0</level2>
					<level3 type="number">0</level3>
					<level4 type="number">0</level4>
					<level5 type="number">0</level5>
					<level6 type="number">0</level6>
					<level7 type="number">0</level7>
					<level8 type="number">0</level8>
					<level9 type="number">0</level9>
				</spellslots>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<h>Faerie Dragon</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="imagewindow" recordname="image.img_faeriedragon_jpg@DD MM Monster Manual">
							<b>Image: </b>Faerie Dragon</link>
					</linklist>
					<p>A faerie dragon is a cat-sized dragon with butterfly wings. It wears a sharp-toothed grin and expresses its delight by the twitching of its tail, its merriment fading only if it is attacked.</p>
					<p>
						<b>
							<i>Invisible Tricksters. </i>
						</b>The only warning of a faerie dragon's presence is a stifled giggle. The dragon stays out of sight, watching invisibly as its victims contend with its pranks. When its fun is done, the dragon might reveal itself, depending on the disposition of its &#34;prey.&#34;</p>
					<p>
						<b>
							<i>Friendly and Bright. </i>
						</b>A faerie dragon has a sharp mind, a fondness for treasure and good company, and a puckish sense of humor. Travelers can play to a faerie dragon's draconic nature by offering it &#34;treasure&#34; in the form of sweets, baked goods, and baubles in exchange for information or safe passage through its territory.</p>
					<p>
						<b>
							<i>The Colors of Age. </i>
						</b>A faerie dragon's scales change hue as it ages, moving through all the colors of the rainbow. All faerie dragons have innate spellcasting ability, gaining new spells as they mature.</p>
					<table>
						<tr>
							<td>
								<b>Dragon Color</b>
							</td>
							<td>
								<b>Age Range</b>
							</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>Red</td>
							<td>5 years or less</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>Orange</td>
							<td>6 -10 years</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>Yellow</td>
							<td>11-20 years</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>Green</td>
							<td>21-30 years</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>Blue</td>
							<td>31- 40 years</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>Indigo</td>
							<td>41-50 years</td>
						</tr>
						<tr>
							<td>Violet</td>
							<td>51 years or more</td>
						</tr>
					</table>
				</text>
				<token type="token">portraits/Companions/Tilrum the stubborn.png</token>
				<token3Dflat type="token">portraits/Tilrum the stubborn.png</token3Dflat>
				<traits>
					<id-00001>
						<desc type="string">As a bonus action, the dragon can magically turn invisible until its concentration ends (as if concentrating on a spell). Any equipment the dragon wears or carries is invisible with it.</desc>
						<name type="string">Superior Invisibility</name>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<desc type="string">Using telepathy, the dragon can magically communicate with any other faerie dragon within 60 feet of it.</desc>
						<name type="string">Limited Telepathy</name>
					</id-00002>
					<id-00003>
						<desc type="string">The dragon has advantage on saving throws against spells and other magical effects.</desc>
						<name type="string">Magic Resistance</name>
					</id-00003>
					<id-00004>
						<desc type="string">The dragon's innate spellcasting ability is Charisma. It can innately cast a number of spells, requiring no material components:\n1/day each: color spray, dancing lights, hallucinatory terrain, mage hand, major image, minor illusion, mirror image, polymorph, suggestion</desc>
						<name type="string">Innate Spellcasting</name>
					</id-00004>
				</traits>
				<type type="string">dragon</type>
				<wounds type="number">0</wounds>
				<xp type="number">450</xp>
			</id-00001>
		</cohorts>
		<coins>
			<id-00001>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
				<name type="string">PP</name>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<amount type="number">2850</amount>
				<name type="string">GP</name>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
				<name type="string">EP</name>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
				<name type="string">SP</name>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<amount type="number">0</amount>
				<name type="string">CP</name>
			</id-00005>
		</coins>
		<defenses>
			<ac>
				<armor type="number">5</armor>
				<dexbonus type="string">max2</dexbonus>
				<disstealth type="number">0</disstealth>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<shield type="number">2</shield>
				<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
				<total type="number">19</total>
			</ac>
		</defenses>
		<deity type="string">Shaundakul- was the patron of those that ventured into uncharted territory and distant lands, including traders, miners, rangers, caravanners, and adventurers.</deity>
		<effectlist />
		<encumbrance>
			<encumbered type="number">100</encumbered>
			<encumberedheavy type="number">200</encumberedheavy>
			<liftpushdrag type="number">600</liftpushdrag>
			<load type="number">98</load>
			<max type="number">300</max>
		</encumbrance>
		<exp type="number">0</exp>
		<expneeded type="number">85000</expneeded>
		<featlist>
			<id-00001>
				<effectlist />
				<hpadd type="number">0</hpadd>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Fey Touched</name>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Your exposure to the Feywild or one of its denizens has left a magical mark on you. You gain the following benefits:</p>
					<list>
						<li>Increase your Intelligence, Wisdom, or Charisma score by 1, to a maximum of 20.</li>
						<li>You learn the misty step spell and one 1st-level spell of your choice. The 1st-level spell must be from the divination or enchantment school of magic. You can cast each of these spells without expending a spell slot. Once you cast either of these spells in this way, you can't cast that spell in this way again until you finish a long rest. You can also cast these spells using spell slots you have of the appropriate level. The spells' spellcasting ability is the ability increased by this feat.</li>
					</list>
				</text>
			</id-00001>
		</featlist>
		<featurelist>
			<id-00001>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Planar Infusion</name>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Living someplace steeped in the energy of the planes, you gain the Scion of the Outer Planes feat (presented later in this document). In addition, you know where to find free, modest lodging and food in the community you grew up in.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Divine Sense</name>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>The presence of strong evil registers on your senses like a noxious odor, and powerful good rings like heavenly music in your ears. As an action, you can open your awareness to detect such forces. Until the end of your next turn, you know the location of any celestial, fiend, or undead within 60 feet of you that is not behind total cover. You know the type (celestial, fiend, or undead) of any being whose presence you sense, but not its identity (the vampire Count Strahd von Zarovich, for instance).</p>
					<p>Within the same radius, you also detect the presence of any place or object that has been consecrated or desecrated, as with the hallow spell.</p>
					<p>You can use this feature a number of times equal to 1 + your Charisma modifier. When you finish a long rest, you regain all expended uses.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<level type="number">5</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Extra Attack</name>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Beginning at 5th level, you can attack twice, instead of once, whenever you take the Attack action on your turn.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Divine Smite</name>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Starting at 2nd level, when you hit a creature with a melee weapon attack, you can expend one spell slot to deal radiant damage to the target, in addition to the weapon's damage. The extra damage is 2d8 for a 1st-level spell slot, plus 1d8 for each spell level higher than 1st, to a maximum of 5d8. The damage increases by 1d8 if the target is an undead or a fiend.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Fighting Style</name>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>At 2nd level, you adopt a style of fighting as your specialty. Choose one of the following options. You can't take a Fighting Style option more than once, even if you later get to choose again.</p>
					<p>
						<b>Defense</b>
					</p>
					<p>While you are wearing armor, you gain a +1 bonus to AC.</p>
					<p>
						<b>Dueling</b>
					</p>
					<p>When you are wielding a melee weapon in one hand and no other weapons, you gain a +2 bonus to damage rolls with that weapon.</p>
					<p>
						<b>Great Weapon Fighting</b>
					</p>
					<p>When you roll a 1 or 2 on a damage die for an attack you make with a melee weapon that you are wielding with two hands, you can reroll the die and must use the new roll. The weapon must have the two-handed or versatile property for you to gain this benefit.</p>
					<p>
						<b>Protection</b>
					</p>
					<p>When a creature you can see attacks a target other than you that is within 5 feet of you, you can use your reaction to impose disadvantage on the attack roll. You must be wielding a shield.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Spellcasting</name>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>By 2nd level, you have learned to draw on divine magic through meditation and prayer to cast spells as a cleric does.</p>
					<p>
						<b>Preparing and Casting Spells</b>
					</p>
					<p>The Paladin table shows how many spell slots you have to cast your spells. To cast one of your paladin spells of 1st level or higher, you must expend a slot of the spell's level or higher. You regain all expended spell slots when you finish a long rest.</p>
					<p>You prepare the list of paladin spells that are available for you to cast, choosing from the paladin spell list. When you do so, choose a number of paladin spells equal to your Charisma modifier + half your paladin level, rounded down (minimum of one spell). The spells must be of a level for which you have spell slots.</p>
					<p>For example, if you are a 5th-level paladin, you have four 1st-level and two 2nd-level spell slots. With a Charisma of 14, your list of prepared spells can include four spells of 1st or 2nd level, in any combination. If you prepare the 1st-level spell cure wounds, you can cast it using a 1st-level or a 2nd-level slot. Casting the spell doesn't remove it from your list of prepared spells.</p>
					<p>You can change your list of prepared spells when you finish a long rest. Preparing a new list of paladin spells requires time spent in prayer and meditation: at least 1 minute per spell level for each spell on your list.</p>
					<p>
						<b>Spellcasting Ability</b>
					</p>
					<p>Charisma is your spellcasting ability for your paladin spells, since their power derives from the strength of your convictions. You use your Charisma whenever a spell refers to your spellcasting ability. In addition, you use your Charisma modifier when setting the saving throw DC for a paladin spell you cast and when making an attack roll with one.</p>
					<p>
						<b>Spell save DC </b>= 8 + your proficiency bonus + your Charisma modifier</p>
					<p>
						<b>Spell attack modifier </b>= your proficiency bonus + your Charisma modifier</p>
					<p>
						<b>Spellcasting Focus</b>
					</p>
					<p>You can use a holy symbol as a spellcasting focus for your paladin spells.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Lay On Hands</name>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Your blessed touch can heal wounds. You have a pool of healing power that replenishes when you finish a Long Rest. With that pool, you can restore a total number of Hit Points equal to five times your Paladin level.</p>
					<p>As a Bonus Action, you can touch a creature (which could be yourself) and draw power from the pool of healing to restore a number of Hit Points to that creature, up to the maximum amount remaining in the pool.</p>
					<p>You can also expend 5 Hit Points from the pool of healing power to remove the Poisoned condition from the creature; those points don't also restore Hit Points to the creature.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<level type="number">6</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Aura of Protection</name>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Starting at 6th level, whenever you or a friendly creature within 10 feet of you must make a saving throw, the creature gains a bonus to the saving throw equal to your Charisma modifier (with a minimum bonus of +1). You must be conscious to grant this bonus.</p>
					<p>At 18th level, the range of this aura increases to 30 feet.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Weapon Mastery</name>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Your training with weapons allows you to use the mastery properties of two kinds of weapons of your choice with which you have proficiency, such as Longswords and Javelins.</p>
					<p>Whenever you finish a Long Rest, you can change the kinds of weapons you chose. For example, you could switch to using the mastery properties of Halberds and Flails.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00009>
			<id-00010>
				<level type="number">3</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Divine Health</name>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>By 3rd level, the divine magic flowing through you makes you immune to disease.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00010>
			<id-00011>
				<level type="number">3</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Sacred Oath</name>
				<specializationchoice type="number">1</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Becoming a paladin involves taking vows that commit the paladin to the cause of righteousness, an active path of fighting wickedness. The final oath, taken when he or she reaches 3rd level, is the culmination of all the paladin's training. Some characters with this class don't consider themselves true paladins until they have reached 3rd level and made this oath. For others, the actual swearing of the oath is a formality, an official stamp on what has always been true in the paladin's heart.</p>
					<p>When you reach 3rd level, you swear the oath that binds you as a paladin forever. Up to this time you have been in a preparatory stage, committed to the path but not yet sworn to it. Now you choose an oath, such as the Oath of Devotion.</p>
					<p>Your choice grants you features at 3rd level and again at 7th, 15th, and 20th level. Those features include oath spells and the Channel Divinity feature.</p>
					<p>
						<b>Breaking Your Oath</b>
					</p>
					<p>A paladin tries to hold to the highest standards of conduct, but even the most virtuous paladin is fallible. Sometimes the right path proves too demanding, sometimes a situation calls for the lesser of two evils, and sometimes the heat of emotion causes a paladin to transgress his or her oath.</p>
					<p>A paladin who has broken a vow typically seeks absolution from a cleric who shares his or her faith or from another paladin of the same order. The paladin might spend an all night vigil in prayer as a sign of penitence, or undertake a fast or similar act of self-denial. After a rite of confession and forgiveness, the paladin starts fresh.</p>
					<p>If a paladin willfully violates his or her oath and shows no sign of repentance, the consequences can be more serious. At the GM's discretion, an impenitent paladin might be forced to abandon this class and adopt another.</p>
					<p>
						<b>Oath Spells</b>
					</p>
					<p>Each oath has a list of associated spells. You gain access to these spells at the levels specified in the oath description. Once you gain access to an oath spell, you always have it prepared. Oath spells don't count against the number of spells you can prepare each day.</p>
					<p>If you gain an oath spell that doesn't appear on the paladin spell list, the spell is nonetheless a paladin spell for you.</p>
					<p>
						<b>Channel Divinity</b>
					</p>
					<p>Your oath allows you to channel divine energy to fuel magical effects. Each Channel Divinity option provided by your oath explains how to use it.</p>
					<p>When you use your Channel Divinity, you choose which option to use. You must then finish a short or long rest to use your Channel Divinity again.</p>
					<p>Some Channel Divinity effects require saving throws. When you use such an effect from this class, the DC equals your paladin spell save DC.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00011>
			<id-00012>
				<level type="number">4</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Ability Score Improvement</name>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>When you reach 4th level, and again at 8th, 12th, 16th, and 19th level, you can increase one ability score of your choice by 2, or you can increase two ability scores of your choice by 1. As normal, you can't increase an ability score above 20 using this feature.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00012>
			<id-00013>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Divine Domain</name>
				<specializationchoice type="number">1</specializationchoice>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Choose one domain related to your deity: Knowledge, Life, Light, Nature, Tempest, Trickery, or War. Each domain is detailed at the end of the class description and each one provides examples of gods associated with it.</p>
					<p>Your choice grants you domain spells and other features when you choose it at 1st level. It also grants you additional ways to use Channel Divinity when you gain that feature at 2nd level, and additional benefits at 6th, 8th, and 17th levels.</p>
					<p>
						<b>Domain Spells</b>
					</p>
					<p>Each domain has a list of spells-its domain spells-that you gain at the cleric levels noted in the domain description. Once you gain a domain spell, you always have it prepared, and it doesn't count against the number of spells you can prepare each day.</p>
					<p>If you have a domain spell that doesn't appear on the cleric spell list, the spell is nonetheless a cleric spell for you.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00013>
		</featurelist>
		<flaws type="string">Obsessed with work of caring and history of the gates . Gives away too much, often to oneâ€™s own detriment.</flaws>
		<gender type="string">Female</gender>
		<height type="string">6' 2"</height>
		<hero type="number">3</hero>
		<hp>
			<adjust type="number">0</adjust>
			<base type="number">134</base>
			<deathsavefail type="number">0</deathsavefail>
			<deathsavesuccess type="number">0</deathsavesuccess>
			<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
			<total type="number">134</total>
			<wounds type="number">0</wounds>
		</hp>
		<ideals type="string">Friendship. Material goods come and go. Bonds of friendship last forever. Redemption. There's a spark of good in everyone.Free Thinking. Inquiry and curiosity are the pillars of progress.</ideals>
		<initiative>
			<misc type="number">0</misc>
			<prof type="number">0</prof>
			<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
			<total type="number">2</total>
		</initiative>
		<inspiration type="number">3</inspiration>
		<inventorylist>
			<id-00001>
				<ac type="number">16</ac>
				<attune type="number">0</attune>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">0</carried>
				<cost type="string">75 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Made of interlocking metal rings, chain mail includes a layer of quilted fabric worn underneath the mail to prevent chafing and to cushion the impact of blows. The suit includes gauntlets.</p>
				</description>
				<dexbonus type="string">-</dexbonus>
				<effectlist />
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Chain Mail</name>
				<stealth type="string">Disadvantage</stealth>
				<strength type="string">Str 13</strength>
				<subtype type="string">Heavy Armor</subtype>
				<type type="string">Armor</type>
				<weight type="number">55</weight>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<attune type="number">0</attune>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">15 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<damage type="string">1d8 radiant</damage>
				<description type="formattedtext" />
				<effectlist />
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Longsword (S)</name>
				<properties type="string">Versatile (1d10), finesse</properties>
				<subtype type="string">Martial Weapons</subtype>
				<type type="string">Weapon</type>
				<weight type="number">3</weight>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<attune type="number">0</attune>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">15 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<damage type="string">1d8 slashing</damage>
				<description type="formattedtext" />
				<effectlist />
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Longsword</name>
				<properties type="string">Versatile (1d10)</properties>
				<subtype type="string">Martial Weapons</subtype>
				<type type="string">Weapon</type>
				<weight type="number">3</weight>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<attune type="number">0</attune>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 sp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<damage type="string">1d6 piercing</damage>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p />
				</description>
				<effectlist />
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Javelin</name>
				<properties type="string">Thrown (range 30/120)</properties>
				<subtype type="string">Simple Melee Weapons</subtype>
				<type type="string">Weapon</type>
				<weight type="number">2</weight>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<attune type="number">0</attune>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">10 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Includes a backpack, a bedroll, a mess kit, a tinderbox, 10 torches, 10 days of rations, and a waterskin. The pack also has 50 feet of hempen rope strapped to the side of it.</p>
				</description>
				<effectlist />
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Explorer's Pack</name>
				<subitems />
				<subtype type="string">Equipment Packs</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">59</weight>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<attune type="number">0</attune>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A holy symbol is a representation of a god or pantheon. It might be an amulet depicting a symbol representing a deity, the same symbol carefully engraved or inlaid as an emblem on a shield, or a tiny box holding a fragment of a sacred relic. The <i>Player's Handbook </i>lists many gods in the multiverse and their typical symbols. A cleric or paladin can use a holy symbol as a spellcasting focus, as described in chapter 10. To use the symbol in this way, the caster must hold it in hand, wear it visibly, or bear it on a shield.</p>
				</description>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Amulet</name>
				<subtype type="string">Holy Symbol</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<attune type="number">0</attune>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">25 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A book might contain poetry, historical accounts, information pertaining to a particular field of lore, diagrams and notes on gnomish contraptions, or just about anything else that can be represented using text or pictures. A book of spells is a spellbook (described later in this section).</p>
				</description>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Book</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard Adventuring Gear</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">5</weight>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<attune type="number">0</attune>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">10 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">2</count>
				<description type="formattedtext" />
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Ink (1-ounce Bottle)</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">0.06</weight>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<attune type="number">0</attune>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 cp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext" />
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Ink Pen</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">0.02</weight>
			</id-00009>
			<id-00010>
				<attune type="number">0</attune>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">2 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Clothes, Traveler's</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard Adventuring Gear</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">4</weight>
			</id-00010>
			<id-00011>
				<attune type="number">0</attune>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">5 sp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A cloth or leather pouch can hold up to 20 sling bullets or 50 blowgun needles, among other things. A compartmentalized pouch for holding spell components is called a component pouch (described earlier in this section).</p>
				</description>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Pouch</name>
				<subtype type="string">Standard Adventuring Gear</subtype>
				<type type="string">Adventuring Gear</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00011>
			<id-00012>
				<attune type="number">0</attune>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p />
				</description>
				<effectlist />
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Coin Dragon </name>
				<weight type="number">0</weight>
			</id-00012>
			<id-00013>
				<ac type="number">2</ac>
				<attune type="number">0</attune>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">50 - 100 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<h>Description</h>
					<p>The front of this shield is shaped in the likeness of a face. While bearing the shield, you can use a bonus action to alter the face's expression.</p>
					<p>
						<b>Shield Notes</b>
					</p>
					<p>A shield is made from wood or metal and is carried in one hand. Wielding a shield increases your Armor Class by 2. You can benefit from only one shield at a time.</p>
				</description>
				<dexbonus type="string">-</dexbonus>
				<effectlist />
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Shield of Expression</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Shield</nonid_name>
				<nonidentified type="string">The front of this shield is shaped in the likeness of a face</nonidentified>
				<properties type="string">Magic</properties>
				<rarity type="string">Common</rarity>
				<spells>
					<id-00001>
						<link type="windowreference">
							<class />
							<recordname />
						</link>
						<name type="string">Shield of Expression</name>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<link type="windowreference">
							<class />
							<recordname />
						</link>
						<name type="string">Shield</name>
					</id-00002>
				</spells>
				<stealth type="string">-</stealth>
				<strength type="string">-</strength>
				<subtype type="string">Shield</subtype>
				<type type="string">Armor</type>
				<weight type="number">6</weight>
			</id-00013>
			<id-00014>
				<attune type="number">0</attune>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<name type="string">A white feather that sheds dim light in a 5-foot radius</name>
				<weight type="number">0</weight>
			</id-00014>
			<id-00015>
				<attune type="number">0</attune>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<name type="string"> Small lead ingot with a strange thumbprint pressed into it that whispers when held tightly</name>
				<weight type="number">0</weight>
			</id-00015>
			<id-00016>
				<attune type="number">0</attune>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<name type="string"> A tiny gnome-crafted music box that plays a song you dimly remember from your childhood</name>
				<weight type="number">0</weight>
			</id-00016>
			<id-00017>
				<attune type="number">0</attune>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<name type="string"> Silver skull the size of a coin</name>
				<weight type="number">0</weight>
			</id-00017>
			<id-00018>
				<attune type="number">0</attune>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p />
				</description>
				<name type="string"> Mosaic tile with a multicolored, glazed surface showing a gate</name>
				<weight type="number">0</weight>
			</id-00018>
			<id-00019>
				<attune type="number">0</attune>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p />
				</description>
				<name type="string">fan that, when unfolded, shows a sleeping cat</name>
				<weight type="number">0</weight>
			</id-00019>
			<id-00020>
				<attune type="number">0</attune>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">50,001 - 100,000 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<h>Description</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="reference_spell" recordname="reference.spelldata.gate@*">
							<b>Spell: </b>Gate</link>
						<link class="reference_spell" recordname="reference.spelldata.planeshift@*">
							<b>Spell: </b>Plane Shift</link>
						<link class="power" recordname="reference.spelldata.createbonfire@DD Tashas Cauldron of Everything - Players">Spell: Create Bonfire</link>
						<link class="power" recordname="reference.spelldata.tenser_sfloatingdisk@DD PHB Deluxe">Spell: Tenser's Floating Disk</link>
						<link class="power" recordname="reference.spelldata.findsteed@DD PHB Deluxe">Spell: Find Steed</link>
					</linklist>
					<p>This cube is 3 inches across and radiates palpable magical energy. The six sides of the cube are each keyed to a different plane of existence, one of which is the Material Plane. The other sides are linked to planes determined by the GM.</p>
					<p>You can use an action to press one side of the cube to cast the <i>gate </i>spell with it (useing 10 points of stored energy), opening a portal to the plane keyed to that side. Alternatively, if you use an action to press one side twice, you can cast the <i>plane shift </i>spell(save DC 17) ( Useing 6 points of energy) with the cube and transport the targets to the plane keyed to that side.&#13;&#13;This items stores 30 points of magical energy to operate.&#13;When empty the cube must be fully powered before it can be used, and can only be refilled when fully empty.&#13;&#13;NOTE: The following 3 spells have been added to the cube in order to help empty the cube if it should not have enough energy to cast Plane Shift or Gate&#13;&#13;Create Bonfire uses 1 Point of stored energy&#13;Tenser's Floating Disk uses 2 points of energy&#13;Find Steed uses 3 points of energy</p>
					<p>&#13;Plane Shift uses 6 Points of stored energy&#13;Gate uses 10 Points of energy&#13;&#13;Side 1 - Keyed to Milicias fathers matching device whereever that may be&#13;Side 2 - Keyed to Mogo neard the only known location of the Mician Village&#13;Side 3 - Keyed - Unknown - Press at you own risk&#13;Side 4 - Keyed - Unknown - Press at you own risk&#13;Side 5 - Keyed - Unknown - Special Condition&#13;Side 6 - Keyed to the pocket dimention one use</p>
					<p />
					<p>_________________________________________________________________________________</p>
				</description>
				<effectlist />
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">â— Cubic Gate Prototype 12/30</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">A strange Cube Device given to Milicia by her father</nonid_name>
				<nonidentified type="string">This cube is made from an unknown material, is about 3 inches across and palpably radiates magic from each of its six faces.</nonidentified>
				<picture type="token">images/Cubic_Gate.jpg@DD Dungeon Masters Guide</picture>
				<properties type="string">Magic</properties>
				<rarity type="string">Legendary (Only Works For Milicia)</rarity>
				<spells>
					<id-00001>
						<link type="windowreference">
							<class />
							<recordname />
						</link>
						<name type="string">Cubic Gate</name>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<link type="windowreference">
							<class />
							<recordname />
						</link>
						<name type="string">Cube</name>
					</id-00002>
				</spells>
				<type type="string">Wondrous Item</type>
				<weight type="number">1</weight>
			</id-00020>
			<id-00021>
				<attune type="number">1</attune>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">50 - 100 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<damage type="string">1d8 slashing, magic, silvered</damage>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<h>Description</h>
					<p>In darkness, the unsheathed blade of this sword sheds moonlight, creating bright light in a 15-foot radius and dim light for an additional 15 feet.&#13;&#13;On a killing blow 1d4 point of energy is transfered to (Dad's Strange Cube)</p>
				</description>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">The Valen Moon</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Shiny Longsword</nonid_name>
				<nonidentified type="string">This sword seems to sparkle with light</nonidentified>
				<properties type="string">magic, silvered, Versatile (1d10), </properties>
				<rarity type="string">Special (Requires Attunement)</rarity>
				<spells>
					<id-00001>
						<link type="windowreference">
							<class />
							<recordname />
						</link>
						<name type="string">Moon-Touched Sword</name>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<link type="windowreference">
							<class />
							<recordname />
						</link>
						<name type="string">Longsword</name>
					</id-00002>
				</spells>
				<subtype type="string">Martial Weapons</subtype>
				<type type="string">Weapon</type>
				<weight type="number">3</weight>
			</id-00021>
			<id-00022>
				<attune type="number">0</attune>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<count type="number">12</count>
				<name type="string">Bracelet (trinket boy ranbow colored silver worth about 1 gp )</name>
				<weight type="number">0</weight>
			</id-00022>
			<id-00023>
				<attune type="number">0</attune>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">5,001 - 50,000 gp</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<h>Description</h>
					<p>While wearing this ring, you regain 1d6 hit points every 10 minutes, provided that you have at least 1 hit point. If you lose a body part, the ring causes the missing part to regrow and return to full functionality after 1d6 + 1 days if you have at least 1 hit point the whole time.</p>
				</description>
				<effectlist />
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Ring of Regeneration</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Ring</nonid_name>
				<nonidentified type="string">A simple band of copper with a stylized pattern of a vine sprouting new growth around its outer surface.</nonidentified>
				<picture type="token"></picture>
				<properties type="string">Magic</properties>
				<rarity type="string">Very Rare</rarity>
				<spells>
					<id-00001>
						<link type="windowreference">
							<class />
							<recordname />
						</link>
						<name type="string">Ring of Regeneration</name>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<link type="windowreference">
							<class />
							<recordname />
						</link>
						<name type="string">Signet Ring</name>
					</id-00002>
				</spells>
				<type type="string">Ring</type>
				<weight type="number">0.01</weight>
			</id-00023>
			<id-00024>
				<attune type="number">0</attune>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<count type="number">12</count>
				<name type="string">Bracelet (trinket girl ranbow colored silver worth about 1 gp )</name>
				<weight type="number">0</weight>
			</id-00024>
			<id-00025>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<attune type="number">0</attune>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>...</p>
				</description>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">! School Uniform 05</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">School Uniform 05</nonid_name>
				<properties type="string">Adaptive - Visualy changes based on enviromental conditions and wearers needs</properties>
				<rarity type="string">Special</rarity>
				<subtype type="string">Adaptive</subtype>
				<type type="string">Armor</type>
				<weight type="number">0</weight>
			</id-00025>
			<id-00026>
				<attune type="number">0</attune>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">0</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Allows Comunication between Linked devices, IE &#34;Party Members&#34;and &#34;Home Base&#34;Can have 12 Active Links Not including &#34;home base&#34;&#13;&#13;Universal translater</p>
				</description>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">! School Ear Piece</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">School Ear Piece 01</nonid_name>
				<rarity type="string">Special</rarity>
				<subtype type="string">Ear</subtype>
				<type type="string">"Jewlery"</type>
				<weight type="number">0</weight>
			</id-00026>
			<id-00027>
				<attune type="number">0</attune>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p />
				</description>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">! School Gear</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">School Gear 01</nonid_name>
				<properties type="string">At Will - Transforms into any basic weapon the registered user can use </properties>
				<rarity type="string">Special</rarity>
				<subtype type="string">Adaptive</subtype>
				<type type="string">Weapon</type>
				<weight type="number">0</weight>
			</id-00027>
			<id-00028>
				<attune type="number">0</attune>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p />
				</description>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">01 Soul Stone</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Soul Stone</nonid_name>
				<nonidentified type="string">Soul Bound</nonidentified>
				<rarity type="string">Special</rarity>
				<subtype type="string">Special</subtype>
				<type type="string">Special</type>
				<weight type="number">0</weight>
			</id-00028>
			<id-00029>
				<attune type="number">0</attune>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<name type="string">Ornate Box of hair accessories</name>
				<weight type="number">0</weight>
			</id-00029>
			<id-00030>
				<attune type="number">0</attune>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<count type="number">12</count>
				<name type="string">Various Ear Rings (made of colored silver)</name>
				<weight type="number">0</weight>
			</id-00030>
			<id-00031>
				<attune type="number">0</attune>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<count type="number">4</count>
				<name type="string">Specialized Ear Jewlery perfectly fitted to Milicia</name>
				<weight type="number">0</weight>
			</id-00031>
			<id-00032>
				<attune type="number">0</attune>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<name type="string">z 2250 yos money</name>
				<weight type="number">0</weight>
			</id-00032>
			<id-00033>
				<attune type="number">0</attune>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<name type="string">Bottle of 20 unknown pills</name>
				<weight type="number">0</weight>
			</id-00033>
			<id-00034>
				<attune type="number">0</attune>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<count type="number">24</count>
				<name type="string">-- Refridgerated bag of holding lasts</name>
				<weight type="number">0</weight>
			</id-00034>
			<id-00035>
				<attune type="number">0</attune>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p />
				</description>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Phoenix Down - Free Revive</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Feather - Unknown</nonid_name>
				<nonidentified type="string">Feather - Unknown</nonidentified>
				<weight type="number">0</weight>
			</id-00035>
			<id-00036>
				<attune type="number">0</attune>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p />
				</description>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Scroll of Tiny Hut</name>
				<weight type="number">0</weight>
			</id-00036>
			<id-00037>
				<ac type="number">0</ac>
				<attune type="number">0</attune>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<cost type="string">888</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Appearance:</p>
					<p>A palm-sized silver-steel breastplate with a sunburst-shaped coin clasp at the center. It&#8217;s strapped with a small leather harness around his belly, shoulders, and tail. When activated, the armor grows with Tilrum, reshaping into a shining golden draconic chestplate as he enlarges.</p>
					<p>Effects:</p>
					<p>Coin Holster Functionality:</p>
					<p>Tilrum&#8217;s lucky coin is secured in the chest clasp, freeing his claws for smug posing, snack holding, and expressive gestures.</p>
					<p>He can still flip the coin - just with his chin.</p>
					<p>No mechanical protection, but +300% heroic swagger.</p>
					<p>Prideful Puff:</p>
					<p>When Milicia succeeds on a saving throw or crits on an attack and Tilrum is nearby, he lets out a proud chirp and puffs up slightly, as if he did it.</p>
					<p>Enchanted Upgrade &#8211; Golden Rise Transformation:</p>
					<p>Once per long rest, Tilrum may activate the Coinplate&#8217;s latent magic.</p>
					<p>When he does:</p>
					<p>He Enlarges to Large size, or to a size appropriate for Milicia to ride.</p>
					<p>Gains a flying speed of 60 ft if he doesn&#8217;t already have one.</p>
					<p>The transformation lasts for up to 8 hours, or until dismissed (no action required).</p>
					<p>While enlarged, Tilrum is considered a viable flying mount in and out of combat.</p>
					<p>His personality remains the same&#8212;just smugger.</p>
					<p>Flavor Notes:</p>
					<p>When activated, the armor flares with golden shimmer as Tilrum takes flight.</p>
					<p>The embedded coin glows like a second sun.</p>
					<p>His voice doesn&#8217;t get deeper&#8212;but he thinks it does.</p>
					<p>Suggested RP Flair (Optional):</p>
					<p>Insists on being called &#8220;Sir Tilrum the Tall&#8221; while enlarged.</p>
					<p>Sometimes refuses to shrink back until someone praises him. (or time runs out)</p>
					<p>Dramatically guards the party from ridges, trees, or rooftops while refusing to sleep.</p>
				</description>
				<dexbonus type="string">Yes</dexbonus>
				<effectlist />
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Tilrumâ€™s Armor â€“ Coinplate of the Watchful Wyrmling</name>
				<nonid_name type="string">Strange tiny armor</nonid_name>
				<rarity type="string">Rare (Requires Attunement By by Tilrum)</rarity>
				<stealth type="string">-</stealth>
				<strength type="string">-</strength>
				<subtype type="string">Special</subtype>
				<type type="string">Armor</type>
				<weight type="number">0.05</weight>
			</id-00037>
			<id-00038>
				<ac type="number">15</ac>
				<attune type="number">0</attune>
				<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<cost type="string">4500</cost>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Appearance &#38; Description:&#13;&#13;Made from Darkened mithral plates over red drake scale underlayer</p>
					<p>This masterfully crafted armor blends the lightweight strength of mithral with the supple resilience of red drakehide. Flexible red scales line the joints&#8212;shoulders, underarms, hips, inner thighs, and elbows&#8212;subtly catching the light beneath the dark matte plates. Each panel is shaped with deliberate care: sleek, functional, and devoid of excessive ornamentation.&#13;&#13;Forged by a smith from the City of Wrath, the piece eschews traditional infernal flair for a controlled, disciplined design. A small stylized sigil representing Wrath&#8212;not as rage, but as willful resolve&#8212;is engraved into the belt buckle and the base of the gorget.&#13;&#13;The armor hums faintly with dormant energy&#8212;heat coiled in stillness, like a warrior waiting for the moment to act.&#13;&#13;Mantle of the Crimson Vow (Passive &#38; Reaction)&#13;&#13;When Milicia is struck by a critical hit, the armor flares with suppressed draconic heat. The attacker takes 1d8 fire damage.&#13;&#13;Once per long rest, Milicia may reroll a failed saving throw against being charmed or frightened (no reaction required). The second roll is made with advantage.&#13;&#13;Voice of Iron (Bonus Action, 1/short rest)&#13;&#13;For a number of rounds equal to proficiency +1, Milicia invokes the armor's latent wrathful resonance.&#13;&#13;Allies within 10 ft gain +1 AC while in range.&#13;&#13;Milicia gains resistance to psychic damage and cannot be disarmed.&#13;&#13;Hellforged Stealthcraft (Passive)&#13;&#13;No disadvantage on Stealth.&#13;&#13;Gains advantage on Stealth checks in dim light or after standing still for 1 round, as the drake scales dull reflection and absorb ambient light.</p>
					<p>Optional Lore Hook:</p>
					<p>&#8220;Crafted in the City of Wrath for a warrior who embodies control over fury, not surrender to it. The artisan who forged it is known for rejecting the chaos of infernal tradition in favor of discipline and honor. This armor is not a weapon&#8212;it is a vow.&#8221;</p>
				</description>
				<dexbonus type="string">Yes  (max 2)</dexbonus>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Drakeweave Mantle of Wrath</name>
				<picture type="token"></picture>
				<properties type="string">Magic</properties>
				<rarity type="string">Unique (Requires Attunement)</rarity>
				<stealth type="string">-</stealth>
				<strength type="string">-</strength>
				<subtype type="string">Heavy Armor</subtype>
				<type type="string">Armor</type>
				<weight type="number">10</weight>
			</id-00038>
			<id-00039>
				<attune type="number">0</attune>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<name type="string">scrap of cloth #18</name>
				<weight type="number">0</weight>
			</id-00039>
			<id-00040>
				<attune type="number">0</attune>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<count type="number">1</count>
				<name type="string">milk # 5</name>
				<weight type="number">0</weight>
			</id-00040>
		</inventorylist>
		<languagelist>
			<id-00001>
				<name type="string">Celestial</name>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<name type="string">Sign Language</name>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<name type="string">Infernal</name>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<name type="string">Orc</name>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<name type="string">Common </name>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<name type="string">Goblin</name>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<name type="string">Abyssal</name>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<name type="string">Deep Speech</name>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<name type="string">Elvish</name>
			</id-00009>
			<id-00010>
				<name type="string">Undercommon</name>
			</id-00010>
			<id-00011>
				<name type="string">Draconic</name>
			</id-00011>
		</languagelist>
		<level type="number">10</level>
		<locked type="number">1</locked>
		<name type="string">Milicia Valen</name>
		<notes type="string">The one-eyed god Gruumshâ€”lord of war and furyâ€”created the first orcs, and even those orcs who turn away from his worship carry his blessings of might and endurance. The same is true of half-orcs. Some half-orcs hear the whispers of Gruumsh in their dreams, calling them to unleash the rage that simmers within them.</notes>
		<pc_label_hero type="string">Hero Point</pc_label_hero>
		<perception type="number">12</perception>
		<perceptionmodifier type="number">0</perceptionmodifier>
		<personalitytraits type="string">Strange events and otherworldly creatures donâ€™t faze me. </personalitytraits>
		<portrait type="token">portraits/PCs/Milicia 01.png</portrait>
		<powergroup>
			<id-00001>
				<name type="string">Class (Paladin)</name>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<name type="string">Species (Half-Orc)</name>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<castertype type="string">memorization</castertype>
				<name type="string">Spells</name>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<name type="string">Spells (Paladin)</name>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<castertype type="string">memorization</castertype>
				<name type="string">Spells (Cleric)</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00008>
				<name type="string">*Power</name>
			</id-00008>
		</powergroup>
		<powermeta>
			<pactmagicslots1>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots1>
			<pactmagicslots2>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots2>
			<pactmagicslots3>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots3>
			<pactmagicslots4>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots4>
			<pactmagicslots5>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots5>
			<pactmagicslots6>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots6>
			<pactmagicslots7>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots7>
			<pactmagicslots8>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots8>
			<pactmagicslots9>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</pactmagicslots9>
			<spellslots1>
				<max type="number">5</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots1>
			<spellslots2>
				<max type="number">2</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots2>
			<spellslots3>
				<max type="number">1</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots3>
			<spellslots4>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots4>
			<spellslots5>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots5>
			<spellslots6>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots6>
			<spellslots7>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots7>
			<spellslots8>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots8>
			<spellslots9>
				<max type="number">0</max>
				<used type="number">0</used>
			</spellslots9>
		</powermeta>
		<powers>
			<id-00001>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">1</bonus>
								<dice type="dice"></dice>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<healtargeting type="string">self</healtargeting>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>When you are reduced to 0 hit points but not killed outright, you can drop to 1 hit point instead. You can't use this feature again until you finish a long rest.</p>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Species (Half-Orc)</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Relentless Endurance</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<label type="string">Divine Sense; Know the location of any celestial, fiend, or undead (also hallow spell) within 60'</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>The presence of strong evil registers on your senses like a noxious odor, and powerful good rings like heavenly music in your ears. As an action, you can open your awareness to detect such forces. Until the end of your next turn, you know the location of any celestial, fiend, or undead within 60 feet of you that is not behind total cover. You know the type (celestial, fiend, or undead) of any being whose presence you sense, but not its identity (the vampire Count Strahd von Zarovich, for instance).</p>
					<p>Within the same radius, you also detect the presence of any place or object that has been consecrated or desecrated, as with the hallow spell.</p>
					<p>You can use this feature a number of times equal to 1 + your Charisma modifier. When you finish a long rest, you regain all expended uses.</p>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Class (Paladin)</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Divine Sense</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">5</bonus>
								<dice type="dice"></dice>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Your blessed touch can heal wounds. You have a pool of healing power that replenishes when you take a long rest. With that pool, you can restore a total number of hit points equal to your paladin level x5.</p>
					<p>As an action, you can touch a creature and draw power from the pool to restore a number of hit points to that creature, up to the maximum amount remaining in your pool.</p>
					<p>Alternatively, you can expend 5 hit points from your pool of healing to cure the target of one disease or neutralize one poison affecting it. You can cure multiple diseases and neutralize multiple poisons with a single use of Lay on Hands, expending hit points separately for each one.</p>
					<p>This feature has no effect on undead and constructs.</p>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Class (Paladin)</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Lay on Hands</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<label type="string">Fighting Style (Archery); ATK: 2,ranged</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>At 2nd level, you adopt a style of fighting as your specialty. Choose one of the following options. You can't take a Fighting Style option more than once, even if you later get to choose again.</p>
					<p>
						<b>Defense</b>
					</p>
					<p>While you are wearing armor, you gain a +1 bonus to AC.</p>
					<p>
						<b>Dueling</b>
					</p>
					<p>When you are wielding a melee weapon in one hand and no other weapons, you gain a +2 bonus to damage rolls with that weapon.</p>
					<p>
						<b>Great Weapon Fighting</b>
					</p>
					<p>When you roll a 1 or 2 on a damage die for an attack you make with a melee weapon that you are wielding with two hands, you can reroll the die and must use the new roll. The weapon must have the two-handed or versatile property for you to gain this benefit.</p>
					<p>
						<b>Protection</b>
					</p>
					<p>When a creature you can see attacks a target other than you that is within 5 feet of you, you can use your reaction to impose disadvantage on the attack roll. You must be wielding a shield.</p>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Class (Paladin)</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Fighting Style (Archery)</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<label type="string">Fighting Style (Dueling); DMG: 2, melee</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>At 2nd level, you adopt a style of fighting as your specialty. Choose one of the following options. You can't take a Fighting Style option more than once, even if you later get to choose again.</p>
					<p>
						<b>Defense</b>
					</p>
					<p>While you are wearing armor, you gain a +1 bonus to AC.</p>
					<p>
						<b>Dueling</b>
					</p>
					<p>When you are wielding a melee weapon in one hand and no other weapons, you gain a +2 bonus to damage rolls with that weapon.</p>
					<p>
						<b>Great Weapon Fighting</b>
					</p>
					<p>When you roll a 1 or 2 on a damage die for an attack you make with a melee weapon that you are wielding with two hands, you can reroll the die and must use the new roll. The weapon must have the two-handed or versatile property for you to gain this benefit.</p>
					<p>
						<b>Protection</b>
					</p>
					<p>When a creature you can see attacks a target other than you that is within 5 feet of you, you can use your reaction to impose disadvantage on the attack roll. You must be wielding a shield.</p>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Class (Paladin)</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Fighting Style (Dueling)</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">0</durmod>
						<label type="string">Fighting Style (Defence); AC:1</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>At 2nd level, you adopt a style of fighting as your specialty. Choose one of the following options. You can't take a Fighting Style option more than once, even if you later get to choose again.</p>
					<p>
						<b>Defense</b>
					</p>
					<p>While you are wearing armor, you gain a +1 bonus to AC.</p>
					<p>
						<b>Dueling</b>
					</p>
					<p>When you are wielding a melee weapon in one hand and no other weapons, you gain a +2 bonus to damage rolls with that weapon.</p>
					<p>
						<b>Great Weapon Fighting</b>
					</p>
					<p>When you roll a 1 or 2 on a damage die for an attack you make with a melee weapon that you are wielding with two hands, you can reroll the die and must use the new roll. The weapon must have the two-handed or versatile property for you to gain this benefit.</p>
					<p>
						<b>Protection</b>
					</p>
					<p>When a creature you can see attacks a target other than you that is within 5 feet of you, you can use your reaction to impose disadvantage on the attack roll. You must be wielding a shield.</p>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Class (Paladin)</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Fighting Style (Protection)</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">Guidance; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You touch one willing creature. Once before the spell ends, the target can roll a d4 and add the number rolled to one ability check of its choice. It can roll the die before or after making the ability check. The spell then ends.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells (Cleric)</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Guidance</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Divination</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric, Druid</source>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<apply type="string">roll</apply>
						<label type="string">Divine Smite; DMG: 2d8 radiant; IFT: TYPE(fiend,undead); DMG:1d8 radiant</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Starting at 2nd level, when you hit a creature with a melee weapon attack, you can expend one spell slot to deal radiant damage to the target, in addition to the weapon's damage. The extra damage is 2d8 for a 1st-level spell slot, plus 1d8 for each spell level higher than 1st, to a maximum of 5d8. The damage increases by 1d8 if the target is an undead or a fiend.</p>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Class (Paladin)</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Divine Smite</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<apply type="string">roll</apply>
						<label type="string">Divine Smite; DMG: 2d8 radiant; IFT: TYPE(fiend,undead); DMG:1d8 radiant</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Starting at 2nd level, when you hit a creature with a melee weapon attack, you can expend one spell slot to deal radiant damage to the target, in addition to the weapon's damage. The extra damage is 2d8 for a 1st-level spell slot, plus 1d8 for each spell level higher than 1st, to a maximum of 5d8. The damage increases by 1d8 if the target is an undead or a fiend.</p>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Class (Paladin)</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Divine Smite</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
			</id-00009>
			<id-00010>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">wisdom</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d8</dice>
								<type type="string">necrotic</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
					<id-00003>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d12</dice>
								<type type="string">necrotic</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">3</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00003>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You point at one creature you can see within range, and the sound of a dolorous bell fills the air around it for a moment. The target must succeed on a Wisdom saving throw or take 1d8 necrotic damage. If the target is missing any of its hit points, it instead takes 1d12 necrotic damage.</p>
					<p>The spell's damage increases by one die when you reach 5th level (2d8 or 2d12), 11th level (3d8 or 3d12), and 17th level (4d8 or 4d12).</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells (Cleric)</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Toll the Dead</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">60 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Necromancy</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric, Warlock, Wizard, Eldritch Knight, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00010>
			<id-00011>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">dexterity</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d8</dice>
								<type type="string">radiant</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Flame-like radiance descends on a creature that you can see within range. The target must succeed on a Dexterity saving throw or take 1d8 radiant damage. The target gains no benefit from cover for this saving throw.</p>
					<p>The spell's damage increases by 1d8 when you reach 5th level (2d8), 11th level (3d8), and 17th level (4d8).</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells (Cleric)</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Sacred Flame</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">60 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric</source>
			</id-00011>
			<id-00012>
				<actions />
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Your training with weapons allows you to use the mastery properties of two kinds of weapons of your choice with which you have proficiency, such as Longswords and Javelins.</p>
					<p>Whenever you finish a Long Rest, you can change the kinds of weapons you chose. For example, you could switch to using the mastery properties of Halberds and Flails.</p>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Class (Paladin)</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Weapon Mastery</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<version type="string">2024</version>
			</id-00012>
			<id-00013>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<label type="string">Divine Health; Immune to disease</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>By 3rd level, the divine magic flowing through you makes you immune to disease.</p>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Class (Paladin)</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Divine Health</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
			</id-00013>
			<id-00014>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<atktype type="string">ranged</atktype>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">4d6</dice>
								<type type="string">radiant</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
					<id-00003>
						<apply type="string">roll</apply>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<label type="string">GRANTADVATK</label>
						<order type="number">3</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00003>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A flash of light streaks toward a creature of your choice within range. Make a ranged spell attack against the target. On a hit, the target takes 4d6 radiant damage, and the next attack roll made against this target before the end of your next turn has advantage, thanks to the mystical dim light glittering on the target until then.</p>
					<p>
						<b>At Higher Levels. </b>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, the damage increases by 1d6 for each slot level above 1st.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">1 round</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Guiding Bolt</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">120 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric</source>
			</id-00014>
			<id-00015>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d4</dice>
								<stat type="string">base</stat>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 bonus action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A creature of your choice that you can see within range regains hit points equal to 1d4 + your spellcasting ability modifier. This spell has no effect on undead or constructs.</p>
					<p>
						<b>
							<i>At Higher Levels. </i>
						</b>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, the healing increases by 1d4 for each slot level above 1st.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Healing Word</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">60 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric</source>
			</id-00015>
			<id-00016>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<heallist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d8</dice>
								<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
								<statmult type="number">1</statmult>
							</id-00001>
						</heallist>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">heal</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A creature you touch regains a number of hit points equal to 1d8 + your spellcasting ability modifier. This spell has no effect on undead or constructs.</p>
					<p>At Higher Levels. When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, the healing increases by 1d8 for each slot level above 1st.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Cure Wounds</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Bard, Cleric, Cleric Life Domain, Druid, Paladin, Ranger</source>
			</id-00016>
			<id-00017>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">ATK: 1d4; SAVE: 1d4; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (a sprinkling of holy water)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You bless up to three creatures of your choice within range. Whenever a target makes an attack roll or a saving throw before the spell ends, the target can roll a d4 and add the number rolled to the attack roll or saving throw.</p>
					<p>
						<b>
							<i>At Higher Levels. </i>
						</b>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, you can target one additional creature for each slot level above 1st.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Bless</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">30 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Enchantment</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric</source>
			</id-00017>
			<id-00018>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<apply type="string">roll</apply>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">DMG: 2d6 radiant; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 bonus action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>The next time you hit a creature with a weapon attack before this spell ends, the weapon gleams with astral radiance as you strike. The attack deals an extra 2d6 radiant damage to the target, which becomes visible if it's invisible, and the target sheds dim light in a 5-foot radius and can't become invisible until the spell ends.</p>
					<p>At Higher Levels. When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 3rd level or higher, the extra damage increases by 1d6 for each slot level above 2nd.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Branding Smite</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Paladin</source>
			</id-00018>
			<id-00019>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<apply type="string">roll</apply>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">DMG: 2d6 thunder; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">strength</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00002>
					<id-00003>
						<label type="string">Prone</label>
						<order type="number">3</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00003>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 bonus action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>The first time you hit with a melee weapon attack during this spell's duration, your weapon rings with thunder that is audible within 300 feet of you, and the attack deals an extra 2d6 thunder damage to the target. Additionally, if the target is a creature, it must succeed on a Strength saving throw or be pushed 10 feet away from you and knocked prone.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Thunderous Smite</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Paladin</source>
			</id-00019>
			<id-00020>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<apply type="string">roll</apply>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">DMG: 1d6 psychic; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<atkmod type="number">0</atkmod>
						<atkprof type="number">1</atkprof>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<savedcmod type="number">0</savedcmod>
						<savedcprof type="number">1</savedcprof>
						<savemagic type="number">1</savemagic>
						<savetype type="string">wisdom</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00002>
					<id-00003>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">Frightened; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">3</order>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00003>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 bonus action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>The next time you hit with a melee weapon attack during this spell's duration, your attack deals an extra 1d6 psychic damage. Additionally, if the target is a creature, it must succeed on a Wisdom saving throw or be frightened of you until the spell ends. As an action, the creature can make a Wisdom check against your spell save DC to steel its resolve and end this spell.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Wrathful Smite</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Paladin</source>
			</id-00020>
			<id-00021>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<atktype type="string">melee</atktype>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">3d10</dice>
								<type type="string">necrotic</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Make a melee spell attack against a creature you can reach. On a hit, the target takes 3d10 necrotic damage.</p>
					<p>At Higher Levels. When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, the damage increases by 1d10 for each slot level above 1st.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Inflict Wounds</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Necromancy</school>
				<source type="string">Cleric</source>
			</id-00021>
			<id-00022>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<label type="string">Aura of Protection; SAVE: [CHA]</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Starting at 6th level, whenever you or a friendly creature within 10 feet of you must make a saving throw, the creature gains a bonus to the saving throw equal to your Charisma modifier (with a minimum bonus of +1). You must be conscious to grant this bonus.</p>
					<p>At 18th level, the range of this aura increases to 30 feet.</p>
				</description>
				<group type="string">Class (Paladin)</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Aura of Protection</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
			</id-00022>
			<id-00023>
				<actions />
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S, M (diamonds worth 300 gp, which the spell consumes)</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You touch a creature that has died within the last minute. That creature returns to life with 1 hit point. This spell can't return to life a creature that has died of old age, nor can it restore any missing body parts.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells (Paladin)</group>
				<level type="number">3</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Revivify</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Necromancy</school>
				<source type="string">Artificer, Druid (Optional), Ranger (optional)</source>
			</id-00023>
			<id-00024>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<apply type="string">roll</apply>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">DMG: 1d6 fire; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<order type="number">2</order>
						<savetype type="string">constitution</savetype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00002>
					<id-00003>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d6</dice>
								<type type="string">fire</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<order type="number">3</order>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00003>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 bonus action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>The next time you hit a creature with a melee weapon attack during the spell's duration, your weapon flares with white-hot intensity, and the attack deals an extra 1d6 fire damage to the target and causes the target to ignite in flames. At the start of each of its turns until the spell ends, the target must make a Constitution saving throw. On a failed save, it takes 1d6 fire damage.</p>
					<p>On a successful save, the spell ends. If the target or a creature within 5 feet of it uses an action to put out the flames, or if some other effect douses the flames (such as the target being submerged in water), the spell ends.</p>
					<p>
						<b>At Higher Levels. </b>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, the initial extra damage dealt by the attack increases by 1d6 for each slot level above 1st.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 minute</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells (Paladin)</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Searing Smite</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Evocation</school>
				<source type="string">Ranger (optional)</source>
			</id-00024>
			<id-00025>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<apply type="string">roll</apply>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">hour</durunit>
						<label type="string">DMG: 1d4; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>A nonmagical weapon you touch becomes a magic weapon. Choose one of the following damage types: acid, cold, fire, lightning, or thunder. For the duration, the weapon has a +1 bonus to attack rolls and deals an extra 1d4 damage of the chosen type when it hits.</p>
					<p>
						<b>At Higher Levels. </b>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 5th or 6th level, the bonus to attack rolls increases to +2 and the extra damage increases to 2d4. When you use a spell slot of 7th level or higher, the bonus increases to +3 and the extra damage increases to 3d4.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 1 hour</duration>
				<group type="string">Spells (Paladin)</group>
				<level type="number">3</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Elemental Weapon</name>
				<prepared type="number">1</prepared>
				<range type="string">Touch</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Transmutation</school>
				<source type="string">Artificer, Druid (Optional), Ranger (optional)</source>
			</id-00025>
			<id-00026>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<atktype type="string">ranged</atktype>
						<type type="string">cast</type>
					</id-00001>
					<id-00002>
						<damagelist>
							<id-00001>
								<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
								<dice type="dice">d8</dice>
								<type type="string">necrotic</type>
							</id-00001>
						</damagelist>
						<type type="string">damage</type>
					</id-00002>
					<id-00003>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<label type="string">NOTE: Can't regain hit points</label>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00003>
					<id-00004>
						<durmod type="number">1</durmod>
						<label type="string">[TRGT]; GRANTDISATK</label>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00004>
				</actions>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>You create a ghostly, skeletal hand in the space of a creature within range. Make a ranged spell attack against the creature to assail it with the chill of the grave. On a hit, the target takes 1d8 necrotic damage, and it can't regain hit points until the start of your next turn. Until then, the hand clings to the target.</p>
					<p>If you hit an undead target, it also has disadvantage on attack rolls against you until the end of your next turn.</p>
					<p>This spell's damage increases by 1d8 when you reach 5th level (2d8), 11th level (3d8), and 17th level (4d8).</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">1 round</duration>
				<group type="string">*Power</group>
				<level type="number">0</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Chill Touch</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">120 feet</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Necromancy</school>
				<source type="string">Eldritch Knight, Sorcerer, Warlock, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00026>
			<id-00027>
				<actions />
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 bonus action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>Briefly surrounded by silvery mist, you teleport up to 30 feet to an unoccupied space that you can see.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Instantaneous</duration>
				<group type="string">Class (Paladin)</group>
				<level type="number">2</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Misty Step</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<ritual type="number">0</ritual>
				<school type="string">Conjuration</school>
				<source type="string">Druid Coast Circle, Eldritch Knight, Sorcerer, Warlock, Wizard, Arcane Trickster</source>
			</id-00027>
			<id-00028>
				<actions>
					<id-00001>
						<durmod type="number">10</durmod>
						<durunit type="string">minute</durunit>
						<label type="string">Detect Magic; (C)</label>
						<order type="number">1</order>
						<targeting type="string">self</targeting>
						<type type="string">effect</type>
					</id-00001>
				</actions>
				<cast type="number">0</cast>
				<castingtime type="string">1 action</castingtime>
				<components type="string">V, S</components>
				<description type="formattedtext">
					<p>For the duration, you sense the presence of magic within 30 feet of you. If you sense magic in this way, you can use your action to see a faint aura around any visible creature or object in the area that bears magic, and you learn its school of magic, if any.</p>
					<p>The spell can penetrate most barriers, but it is blocked by 1 foot of stone, 1 inch of common metal, a thin sheet of lead, or 3 feet of wood or dirt.</p>
				</description>
				<duration type="string">Concentration, up to 10 minutes</duration>
				<group type="string">Class (Paladin)</group>
				<level type="number">1</level>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Detect Magic</name>
				<prepared type="number">0</prepared>
				<range type="string">Self</range>
				<ritual type="number">1</ritual>
				<school type="string">Divination</school>
				<source type="string">Artificer</source>
			</id-00028>
		</powers>
		<profbonus type="number">4</profbonus>
		<proficiencylist>
			<id-00001>
				<name type="string">Armor: Heavy</name>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<name type="string">Armor: Light</name>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<name type="string">Armor: Medium</name>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<name type="string">Armor: Shields</name>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<name type="string">Weapon: Martial</name>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<name type="string">Weapon: Simple</name>
			</id-00006>
		</proficiencylist>
		<race type="string">Half-Orc</race>
		<racelink type="windowreference">
			<class>reference_race</class>
			<recordname>reference.racedata.half_orc@DD5E SRD Data</recordname>
		</racelink>
		<senses type="string">Darkvision 60</senses>
		<size type="string">Medium</size>
		<skilllist>
			<id-00001>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Athletics</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<shortcut type="number">0</shortcut>
				<stat type="string">strength</stat>
				<total type="number">9</total>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Insight</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<shortcut type="number">0</shortcut>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">6</total>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Intimidation</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<shortcut type="number">0</shortcut>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">7</total>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Persuasion</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<shortcut type="number">0</shortcut>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">7</total>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Survival</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<shortcut type="number">0</shortcut>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">6</total>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Perception</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<shortcut type="number">0</shortcut>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">2</total>
			</id-00006>
			<id-00007>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Arcana</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<shortcut type="number">0</shortcut>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">1</total>
			</id-00007>
			<id-00008>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Nature</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<shortcut type="number">0</shortcut>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">1</total>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00009>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Medicine</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<shortcut type="number">0</shortcut>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">2</total>
			</id-00009>
			<id-00010>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Performance</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<shortcut type="number">0</shortcut>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">3</total>
			</id-00010>
			<id-00011>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Acrobatics</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<shortcut type="number">0</shortcut>
				<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
				<total type="number">2</total>
			</id-00011>
			<id-00012>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Religion</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<shortcut type="number">0</shortcut>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">1</total>
			</id-00012>
			<id-00013>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Sleight of Hand</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<shortcut type="number">0</shortcut>
				<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
				<total type="number">2</total>
			</id-00013>
			<id-00014>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Deception</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<shortcut type="number">0</shortcut>
				<stat type="string">charisma</stat>
				<total type="number">3</total>
			</id-00014>
			<id-00015>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Investigation</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<shortcut type="number">0</shortcut>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">1</total>
			</id-00015>
			<id-00016>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Stealth</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<shortcut type="number">0</shortcut>
				<stat type="string">dexterity</stat>
				<total type="number">2</total>
			</id-00016>
			<id-00017>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">History</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<shortcut type="number">0</shortcut>
				<stat type="string">intelligence</stat>
				<total type="number">1</total>
			</id-00017>
			<id-00018>
				<misc type="number">0</misc>
				<name type="string">Animal Handling</name>
				<prof type="number">0</prof>
				<shortcut type="number">0</shortcut>
				<stat type="string">wisdom</stat>
				<total type="number">2</total>
			</id-00018>
		</skilllist>
		<speed>
			<armor type="number">0</armor>
			<base type="number">30</base>
			<misc type="number">0</misc>
			<temporary type="number">0</temporary>
			<total type="number">30</total>
		</speed>
		<subracelink type="windowreference">
			<class />
			<recordname />
		</subracelink>
		<temp />
		<token type="token">portraits/PCs/Milicia Token 01.png</token>
		<token3Dflat type="token"></token3Dflat>
		<traitlist>
			<id-00001>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Darkvision</name>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>Thanks to your orc blood, you have superior vision in dark and dim conditions. You can see in dim light within 60 feet of you as if it were bright light, and in darkness as if it were dim light. You can't discern color in darkness, only shades of gray.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Menacing</name>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>You gain proficiency in the Intimidation skill.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Relentless Endurance</name>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>When you are reduced to 0 hit points but not killed outright, you can drop to 1 hit point instead. You can't use this feature again until you finish a long rest.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<name type="string">Savage Attacks</name>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<p>When you score a critical hit with a melee weapon attack, you can roll one of the weapon's damage dice one additional time and add it to the extra damage of the critical hit.</p>
				</text>
			</id-00004>
		</traitlist>
		<units />
		<vehicles />
		<weaponlist>
			<id-00001>
				<attackbonus type="number">0</attackbonus>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<damagelist>
					<id-00001>
						<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
						<dice type="dice">d8</dice>
						<stat type="string">base</stat>
						<type type="string">radiant</type>
					</id-00001>
				</damagelist>
				<handling type="number">0</handling>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<maxammo type="number">0</maxammo>
				<name type="string">Longsword (S)</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<properties type="string">Versatile (1d10), finesse</properties>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>item</class>
					<recordname>....inventorylist.id-00002</recordname>
				</shortcut>
				<type type="number">0</type>
			</id-00001>
			<id-00002>
				<attackbonus type="number">0</attackbonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<damagelist>
					<id-00001>
						<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
						<dice type="dice">d8</dice>
						<stat type="string">base</stat>
						<type type="string">slashing</type>
					</id-00001>
				</damagelist>
				<handling type="number">1</handling>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<maxammo type="number">0</maxammo>
				<name type="string">Longsword</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<properties type="string">Versatile (1d10)</properties>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>item</class>
					<recordname>....inventorylist.id-00003</recordname>
				</shortcut>
				<type type="number">0</type>
			</id-00002>
			<id-00003>
				<attackbonus type="number">0</attackbonus>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<damagelist>
					<id-00001>
						<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
						<dice type="dice">d6</dice>
						<stat type="string">base</stat>
						<type type="string">piercing</type>
					</id-00001>
				</damagelist>
				<handling type="number">0</handling>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<maxammo type="number">0</maxammo>
				<name type="string">Javelin</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<properties type="string">Thrown (range 30/120)</properties>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>item</class>
					<recordname>....inventorylist.id-00004</recordname>
				</shortcut>
				<type type="number">0</type>
			</id-00003>
			<id-00004>
				<ammo type="number">0</ammo>
				<attackbonus type="number">0</attackbonus>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<damagelist>
					<id-00001>
						<bonus type="number">0</bonus>
						<dice type="dice">d6</dice>
						<stat type="string">base</stat>
						<type type="string">piercing</type>
					</id-00001>
				</damagelist>
				<handling type="number">0</handling>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<maxammo type="number">0</maxammo>
				<name type="string">Javelin</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<properties type="string">Thrown (range 30/120)</properties>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>item</class>
					<recordname>....inventorylist.id-00004</recordname>
				</shortcut>
				<type type="number">2</type>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00005>
				<attackbonus type="number">1</attackbonus>
				<carried type="number">2</carried>
				<damagelist>
					<id-00001>
						<bonus type="number">1</bonus>
						<dice type="dice">d8</dice>
						<stat type="string">base</stat>
						<statmult type="number">1</statmult>
						<type type="string">slashing, magic, silvered, silver</type>
					</id-00001>
				</damagelist>
				<handling type="number">0</handling>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<masteryknown type="number">0</masteryknown>
				<name type="string">The Valen Moon</name>
				<prof type="number">1</prof>
				<properties type="string">Versatile (1d10), magic, silvered</properties>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>item</class>
					<recordname>....inventorylist.id-00021</recordname>
				</shortcut>
				<type type="number">0</type>
			</id-00005>
			<id-00006>
				<attackbonus type="number">0</attackbonus>
				<carried type="number">1</carried>
				<damagelist />
				<handling type="number">0</handling>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
				<name type="string">! School Gear</name>
				<properties type="string">At Will - Transforms into any basic weapon the registered user can use </properties>
				<shortcut type="windowreference">
					<class>item</class>
					<recordname>....inventorylist.id-00027</recordname>
				</shortcut>
				<type type="number">0</type>
			</id-00006>
		</weaponlist>
		<weight type="string">220</weight>
	</character>
</root>